royalimages.in 2014-10-22

# Privacy Policy

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. The following policies are only in effect for the Web pages, newsletters, discussion lists and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by Royal Images Catalogue Company. The following discloses our Privacy Policy.

**What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it?**

Every computer connected to the Internet is given an "Internet Protocol" IP address. When a visitor requests a page from anywhere within the Onemi website, our servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, but do not collect and evaluate this information for individuals. Our servers do not record e-mail addresses of the visitors and the only email addresses collected are those submitted by a visitor upon becoming a member of Onemi, which are required for membership, however these are not used for anything other than the normal purposes of being a Onemi member, such as our infrequent newsletters, competition results and the likes, no email address would ever be used for any other purpose.

**What are Cookies?**

A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies do not damage your computer system. The only cookie system Onemi implements is in the form of a hit counter in order to see how many daily visitors we have, some of our advertisers may also implement cookie systems, to identify which areas of our websites you have visited, so that the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. Our advertisers may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our Sites. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at other web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

**What other information do you request?**

We may also request your e-mail address or mailing address for the purposes of security or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to the Onemi e-mail newsletter, announcement list or for the directory). Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested. We maintain a zero tolerance "No-Spam" policy that means that we do not intend to sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent. In addition, Onemi will not send you email that you have not agreed to receive. We may from time to time send an e-mail announcing new Onemi products and services. If you choose to supply your postal address in an online form, your email address will not be used for mailings unless you specifically ask for that.

When you enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. Again, it will not be used in any other way but to inform you if you have won or not!

**What information do you collect when I purchase something?**

If you purchase anything from Onemi website, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. However, the credit card number and other details will not be stored by us, they will be used by our Payment Gateway providers to fulfill your online transation on our website.

**Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties?**

Onemi will disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:

Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on an Onemi website.  
Protect and defend the rights or property of Onemi, or visitors to an Onemi website.  
Identify persons who may be violating the law, the legal notice, or the rights of third parties.  
Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.  
Onemi uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. Onemi reserves the right to transfer information in connection with the sale of all or part of Onemi’s capital stock or assets. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. Onemi also links to a wide variety of other sites and contains advertisements owned by third parties. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users See below

**What else should I know about my privacy when online?**

Onemi contains many links to other Web sites and although we makes every effort to ensure only safe links are available, Onemi is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Onemi does not share any of the individual personal information provided to Onemi with the sites to which Onemi links, the only information shared if necessary would be aggregate data (such as how many people use our Site).

Please check with those sites to determine their privacy policy.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example through e-mail, discussion lists, or elsewhere - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return, but you will not from Onemi.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful who you share it with and be responsible whenever you're online.

Your Consent To This Agreement

By using the Onemi website, you consent to the collection and use of information by Onemi as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How can you make changes to any inaccurate information on our website?**

To correct or update any information you have provided, our sites allow you to do it online. In the event of loss of access details you can use any of the following options:

Send an e-mail to cservice@onemi.in   
You can reach us at: +91 (44) 2836 0151. Toll free: 1800-102-2770.

Policy Updates:

We reserve the right to change or update this policy at any time by placing a prominent notice on our site. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to this site.

You are can offer your views, suggestions, if any, by submitting the filled in feedback form online.

**Contact Information**

You can contact us at:

**ONEMI**  
Alsa Regency,   
165 Eldams Road Alwarpet,   
Chennai - 600018 Tamilnadu,   
India. Tel:+91 (44) 2836 0151.  
Email:cservice@onemi.co.in
